Guide to the Records of the Asian/Pacific/American Institute RG.21.35
New York University Archives
Records of the Asian/Pacific/American Institute
1994-2003
RG.21.35
New York University Archives
15.0 Cubic feet
The records of the Asian/Pacific/American (A/P/A) Institute, dated 1994-2004, document the activities of the Institute and reflect student events, faculty affairs and collaboration with the A/P/A studies program. The collection contains photographs, memoranda, correspondence, student surveys, meeting and conference agendas, syllabi, proposals, posters, flyers, and brochures. It also includes audio cassettes, VHS tapes, and mini DVs.
Cabalda, Sheelagh
Geron, Tomio
Morimoto, Risa
Arrangement
Collection is organized into four series:
I. Conference
II. Administrative
III. Events
IV. Photographs
Provenance
Materials transferred to the University Archives in 2007.
Access Restrictions
There may be some restrictions on the use of the collection. For more information, contact: New York University Archives Elmer Holmes Bobst Library 70 Washington Square South New York, NY 10012
Historical/Biographical Note
The Asian/Pacific/American (A/P/A) Institute was founded in 1996 in response to student interest combined with New York University’s commitment to global excellence. The Institute is focused on community and intercultural studies within a broad, rigorous international and comparative framework.
The A/P/A Institute incorporates the ideas of the NYU Asian/Pacific/American studies program and local, national, and international affairs into public events and symposia for the larger New York University and New York City communities. The Institute brings together accomplished scholars, community-builders, and artists from New York City and beyond for events throughout the year including conferences, seminars, book readings, film screenings, musical performances, and brown bag lunches. The Institute also co-sponsors events with student and community organizations, which serve as educational programs to complement the academic Program and address the needs of the community at large.
The A/P/A collaborated on several events and activities with the Office for African American, Latino, and Asian American Student Services (OASIS). OASIS was created in 1988 in response to the expressed needs of students of color for more University administrative support and commitment. Today the mission of OASIS continues to be carried out by the Center for Multicultural Education and Programs (CMEP) at NYU.
Sources:
New York University. “Asian/Pacific/American Studies: The Institute.” http://www.apa.nyu.edu
New York University. “Center for Multicultural Education and Programs: About Us.” http://www.cmep.nyu.edu
Scope and Content Note
The records of the Asian/Pacific/American (A/P/A) Institute, dated 1994-2004, document the activities of the Institute from its founding in 1996 and reflect student events, faculty affairs and collaboration with the A/P/A studies program. The collection contains photographs, memoranda, correspondence, student surveys, meeting and conference agendas, syllabi, proposals, posters, flyers, and brochures. It also includes audio cassettes, VHS tapes, and mini DVs.
The collection is divided into four series: 1. Conference; 2. Administrative; 3. Events; and 4. Photographs.
Series I: Conference. Series contains information on the preparation and production of the Asians in America conference from 1994-1998, as well as other conferences of interest to the A/P/A community. The records generally pertain to conference logistics, planning, and publicity.
Series II: Administrative. Series is divided into three subseries which relate to specific A/P/A staff members.
Subseries A: Sheelagh Cabalda. Contains records pertaining to Cabalda's work at the Office for African American, Latino and Asian American Student Services (OASIS) and in collaboration with A/P/A. This subseries documents various conferences, workshops and events produced by OASIS, A/P/A and other institutions. These records provide an understanding of student activities and events related to A/P/A Institute.
Subseries B: Tomio Geron. Contains correspondence, memoranda and reports related to the further development of the A/P/A studies program, major and minor. This includes new course proposals, staff and faculty job descriptions, mission statement, departmental magazine and creation of an alumni association. These records reflect the planning involved in the ongoing development of the academic program.
Subseries C: Risa Morimoto. Includes general course information related to the A/P/A program in addition to various events sponsored by the department. This subseries contains syllabi, course evaluations, course proposals and event records.
Series III: Events. Series consists of information regarding various events and activities produced and sponsored by the A/P/A Institute. These records are primarily comprised of outreach materials such as posters, brochures, and flyers. The majority of these events are art related, such as gallery exhibitions, author reading series, and film screenings. Events also include lectures and discussions regarding various issues relevant to the A/P/A student community. Many of these events were documented either on film or audio. These recordings are included in the collection. This series is divided into three subseries: 1. General (alphabetical), 2. Posters, and 3. General (chronological). Subseries 3 consists of general events material that was recieved at a later date and its chronological organization has been retained.
Series IV: Photographs. This series includes images of various events, students, faculty, and staff of the A/P/A Institute and the A/P/A studies program.
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Administrative records.; Asian American college students; Memoranda; New York (State)--New York; New York University; New York University. Faculty.; Photographs; Posters; Student activities--New York (N.Y.); Syllabi
- Series I: Conference
  - Abstracts, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abstracts, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abstracts, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abstracts: Accepted, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Abstracts: Rejected, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Advertising and Publicity, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Advertising and Publicity, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Advertising and Publicity, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Advertising and Publicity, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Advisory Board, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Budget, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Compendium Proposal, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Contacts, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Development, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Diversity Resource Collaborative, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Evaluation Forms, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - General, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - General, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - General, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - General, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Logistics, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Logistics, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Logistics, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Logistics, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Notes, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Notes, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Notes, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Other Conferences, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Other Conferences, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Other Conferences, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Other Conferences, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Other Conferences, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Other Conferences, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Other Conferences, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Panel: On Common Ground, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Panelist Biographies, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Panelist Biographies, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Panelist Biographies, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Papers, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Planning, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Proceedings, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Programs, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Programs, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Publicity, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Registration, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Registration, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Registration, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Registration, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Signage, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Tasks, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Volunteers, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Volunteers and Committees, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Workshops, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Series II: Administrative
  - Subseries A: Sheelagh Cabalda, Office for African American, Latino and Asian American Student Services (OASIS)
    - Asia Pacific Conference on Student Affairs, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Asian America Notes Newsletter, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Asian American Student Focus Group Results, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Asian Cultural Union at NYU Publications, 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Asian Cultural Workshops, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Asian Heritage Month, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Asian Pacific American Student Services, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Asian Pacific American Student Services, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Asian Pacific American Student Services: Retreat, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Conferences: General, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Course Descriptions, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Cultural Affairs, 1996-1997, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Diversity, Community, and Intellectual Development Conference, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Diversity Weekend, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Diversity Workshop, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - East Coast Asian Student Union Conference, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - East Coast Asian Student Union Conference, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Educational/Cultural Program, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - FACTS Meeting Information, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Faculty Meeting Agenda, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Gender Issues Weekend Seminar, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Independent Study Focusing on Multiculturalism at NYU, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      Restriction
      Unpublished student paper
    - International Academic Credential Guide, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Leadership Institute, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Life After NYU Lecture Series, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - LINKS Grant, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      Restrictions
      Folder contains restricted financial information.
    - Mailing Lists and Resource Guide, 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Multicultural Initiative Task Force, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Multicultural Leadership Weekend, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - National Conference on Race and Ethnicity in American Higher Education, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - National Diversity Summit Teleconference, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - New Student Orientation, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Nia Awards Ceremony, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Folder contains student nomination forms with contact information.
    - NODA Conference, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - OASIS Focus Group, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Program Development Forms, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Research, 1989-1996, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Residence Life Conference, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Resident Assistant Meeting, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Semester Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Statistics on Students of Color and Majors, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Student Associations Budget, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      Folder contains financial information.
    - Student Leaders of Color Meeting, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Student Papers: Unpublished, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      Folder contains unpublished student papers.
    - Student Power Movement, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Student Surveys, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Substance Abuse Committee, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - TSOA Student Affairs, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Under One Roof Seminar, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Under One Roof Seminar, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Under One Roof Seminar, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - The Wagner Review, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Washington Square News Coverage, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - World AIDS Day Committee, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Subseries B: Tomio Geron, Academic Program Coordinator Asian/Pacific/American Studies Program
    - Alumni Association, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Area/Ethnic Studies, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Artist Programs, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Asian American Media Archives, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Asian American Related Video Collections, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Asian Council and EQUAL Commission, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Asian Pacific American Studies: Major Development, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Asian Pacific American Studies: Minor Program Proposal, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Asian Pacific American Studies: Program Meeting, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Asian Pacific American Studies: Retreat Agenda, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Asian Pacific American Studies: Scripts, circa 1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Campomanes, Oscar, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      Folder contains financial information
    - Challenge Fund Grant Application, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Chinese Construction Workers at NYU, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Folder includes financial/budget information.
    - Correspondence (incoming and outgoing): Dean Santirocco, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Co-Sponsorship, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Co-Sponsorship, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Course Descriptions, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Course Evaluations, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Course Proposal, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Curriculum Plan, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Directors Undergraduate Study Meeting Schedule, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - East of California Network, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Events, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Faculty Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Follow Up Items, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Internal Sessions, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - International Visitors Program, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Mission Guidelines, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Office Renovations: General, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Office Renovations: Furniture, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Pan-a-Visions Newsletter: Meeting, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Pan-A-Visions Newsletter: Overview, circa 1998 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Petitions, circa 1998 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Personnel Meeting Agenda, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Post-doctoral Fellow Paper Proposal, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Program Coordinator Position, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Public Events, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Public Programming: Maya Lin, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Publicity, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Reports and Memos: General, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Research, circa 1997 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Research Assistant Job Description, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Staff Meeting Notes, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Student Coordinators, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Student Surveys, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 51)
      Surveys are not anonymous and include student name and contact information. Only survey results should be made available to researchers.
    - Student Surveys, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Working Session: Colonialism, Diaspora, and the Americas, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Working Session: Community Documentation, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Working Session: Community Studies and Curriculum, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Working Session: Curriculum, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Working Session: South Asian American Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Subseries C: Risa Morimoto, Administrator and Asian/Pacific/American Institute Coordinator
    - Artist-in-Residence: General, Undated, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Artist-in-Residence: Jessica Hagedorn, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Artists Series, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Asian Pacific American Archives and Media Center, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Asian Pacific American Book Collection, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Asian Pacific American Studies Minor, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Asians in America Conference: General, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Asians in America Conference: Planning, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Association for Asian American Studies, 1997-1998; Folder contains 1 VHS tape. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Audre Lorde Project, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Budget Proposal, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Restricted
    - Budget Proposal, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Cantonese I Course: Planning, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Cantonese II Course: Approval Form, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Challenge Fund Grant, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Community Documentation, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Co-Sponsorships, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Course Evaluations, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Course Evaluations, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Course Evaluations, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Course Proposals, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Course Proposals, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Courses, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Curriculum Planning, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Development: Notes, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Development Correspondence: General, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Development Correspondence: American Express, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Development Correspondence: Anheuser-Busch, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Development Correspondence (outgoing): Anna Sui, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Development Correspondence: Bell Atlantic, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Development Correspondence: Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Development Correspondence: Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Development Correspondence: Lucent Technologies, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Development Correspondence: Starr Foundation, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Development Correspondence (outgoing): Vivienne Tam, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Development Correspondence (outgoing): Yahoo, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - East of California Conference, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - East of California Conference, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - East of California Conference, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - East of California Conference, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - East of California Conference, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - East of California Conference, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - East of California Conference: Logistics, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - East of California Conference: Proposals, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - East of California Conference: Workshop, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - End of the Year Party Logistics, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Event: Dangerous Music, Fierce Women, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Event: "Maya Lin: Topologies", 1998 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Event Planning, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Fall Courses: Evaluation Results, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Fall Courses: Listings, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Fall Courses: Listings, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Fall Courses: Listings, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Fall Courses: Proposals, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Fall Courses: Proposals, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Intermediate Tagalog II Course Proposal, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Interoffice Memoranda, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Jan Lo Shinebourne Reception, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - JANM Talk, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - JANM/Jewish Talk, 1997-1998; Folder includes 1 computer disc. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - JANM Workshops, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Keep Event, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Kelly Loves Tony Film Screening, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Kerri Sakamoto Reading, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Letters to Thien Film Screening, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Life After NYU Series, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - NYU Departmental Events, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - NYU Publications, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Open House, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Open House, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Opening of A/P/A Studies Program and Institute, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Program and Curriculum Plan, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Program Budget, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Proposed Courses, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Publicity, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Reading Race and Representation, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Sino-American Training Project, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Small Events and Co-Sponsorships, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - South Asia Pilot, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Spring Courses: General, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Spring Courses: Enrollment, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Spring Courses: Proposals, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Spring Reception, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Spring Syllabi, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Summer Course Listings, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Syllabus: Cinema of Asia-America, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Syllabus: Conversational Tagalog I, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Syllabus: Filming Asia America, Documenting Community, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Syllabus: Media and Culture, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Tagalog Course Instructor Resumes, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Tomie Arai Exhibit Opening Reception, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Visiting Faculty Program, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Visiting Scholars: General, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Visiting Scholar: Anju Bhargava, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Visiting Scholar: Doris Lee, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Visiting Scholar: Fabiana Chin, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Visiting Scholar: Gloria Lee, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Visiting Scholar: Grace Hong, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Visiting Scholar: Margo Machida, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Visiting Scholar: Mimi Young, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Visiting Scholar: Sonny Ago, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Visiting Scholar: Sunaina Maira, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Visiting Scholar: Tan A. Lin, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Visiting Scholar: Tarry Hum, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Visiting Scholar: Tineke Jansen, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Working Sessions, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Series III: Events, 1995-2003
  - Subseries A: General (Alphabetical)
    - Alumni Gallery Viewing, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Annual Holiday Party, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Annual Holiday Party, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Annual Holiday Party, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Artist in Residence: David Henry Hwang, 2000; 2 mini DV and 1 Hi8. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Artist in Residence: Jessica Hagedorn, 1998; Folder contains one VHS tape. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Artist in Residence: Ping Chong, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Artist Talk: Corky Lee, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Artist Talk: Corky Lee: Asian Americans and the Vietnam War, 2003; Folder consists of 1 VHS tape. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Artist Talk: Mary Ting, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Artist Talk: Serene Ford Northington, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 11)